〈（潤平）マジかよ
まさか　よりによって　この俺に〉
Is this for real?!
Is this really happening to me?!
〈こんなことが？〉
（少女）高坂君　あのね…
Kousaka-kun, I...
It's a bit embarrassing, but I...
恥ずかしいんだけど　実は私…
えッ？
ああ～ッ　もう　我慢できない！
I can't hold back anymore!
私のこと　嫌い？
いや　嫌いじゃない
Do you hate me?
No, I don't! I don't hate you at all!
全然　嫌いじゃない
けど　心の準備が…
B-But I'm not emotionally ready!
Love me a lot.
たっぷり　かわいがって
うわあ～ッ！　こら　ニャムサス
Hey! Nyamsus!
部屋に入るなって言ってんだろ
このバカ猫！
I told you not to come into my room!
You dumb cat!
俺が猫アレルギーなの知ってて
わざとか？
Did you do this deliberately, knowing I'm allergic to cats?!
（ニャムサス）フンッ
ギャーギャー小娘みたいに
Yapping like a girl.
器の小さな男だね
You've got no courage.
This is no time to be spacing out.
鼻の下
伸ばしてる場合じゃないだろ
You sinner.
この罰当たりが
マジかよ
Is this for real?
〈俺　まだ夢見てんのか？〉
Am I still dreaming?
ano sora e kimi to hashiri dasou
I'll dash towards the sky.
negaigoto zenbu kanaete ageru
I'll make all your wishes come true.
areya koreya to oshiyosete
Troubles engulfed me at every turn,
itsuno manika nichijou goodbye
and my normal days were gone before I knew it.
anote konote neko tedasuke
I help the cats with this and that.
guruguru mawaru triangle
The triangle whirls around me.
ukauka shite rarenai
There's no time to waste.
isoganakya ikenaitte
I'd better hurry.
kimi eno omoi mo sou nandaka karamawari da
My feelings towards you are spinning in circles.
tsuite nai koto mo
An unfortunate event
ookina chance ni naru kamo shirenai
might prove to be a big opportunity.
kimi no egao ga mireta nara kitto
If I get to see your smile,
nyan toka narutte mae wo muite miyou
I'll try to believe everything will be fine.
masa ni nyan darou
It's really a cat's power.
itsuka kono te todokimasu you ni
May this hand reach you some day.
negaigoto zenbu kanaete miseru yo
I'll really make all your wishes come true.
Cat 01!
The Ugly Cat and the
Cursed High Schooler
（キャスター）それでは　お天気です
Now, on to the weather.
９月半ばとはいえ
まだまだ暑い日が続きますが
It's already mid-September, but there are more warm days ahead.
本日も全国的に晴れ…
Skies will be clear throughout the country.
Good! It's another clear day!
（鈴）よしッ　今日もお天気だ
Suzu, hurry and finish your breakfast.
（母）鈴　早く食べちゃいなさい
は～い→
Okay.
あッ　潤平兄ちゃん　おはよう
Oh, morning, Junpei.
Your cat detector sure is sensitive.
相変わらず　すごいね　猫センサー
ちょっと　ご飯は？
いらね
Hey, what about breakfast?
No thanks.
朝から食卓にアレルゲンって
拷問かよ
The allergy source is at the table this morning.
What torture.
まあ　高坂家全員
猫好きだってのに　何だろうねえ
Sheesh, the entire Takasaka family loves cats. What's with you?
ニャムサス
こんなにかわいいのにね
Nyamsus is so cute!
さあ　お食べ
お兄ちゃんの分まで
Here, eat up all of Junpei's tasty food!
（鈴・母）キャ～ッ！
See ya.
行ってきます
〈ここまでは俺の日常〉
This was my normal routine...
until now.
〈だった　けど…〉
But...
≪（猫Ａ）サンロードのお肉屋さんで…
≪（猫Ｂ）いいわね～
...going to the butcher in Sun Road to...
That sounds great.
〈異変に気づいたのは　ゆうべ〉
I noticed the change last night.
What can I do?
どうしよう　俺…
I...
猫の言葉がわかる！
I can understand what cats say!
（晴彦）そんで　また乱入されて
結局　ボコられたじゃん
After that, he charged in anyway and got his ass kicked.
（晃太）ありゃ　なかったよな
流すな！
That was so dumb.
Don't ignore me!
いるよね～　そういう親バカ
Yeah, I know that kind of pet owner.
「ウチのタマちゃんがママ大好きって
言うんでちゅ　ブリブリドッキュン」とかさ
"Our Tama says he loves me! Oh my, I wuv him!" Like that.
Suppose they do talk. What about?
で　仮に話したとして　どんなん？
えッ　例えば…
Like...
《今日はね　サンロードのお肉屋さんで》
Today, I'm going to the butcher in Sun Road to beg for food.
《ごちそう
おねだりするつもりなの》
That sounds great.
《いいわね～》
《でしょう？》
Doesn't it?
Like that.
とか…
そんでな　また連コインされて
ありゃ　なかったよな～
Then he started putting more coins in the game.
He's such a moron.
I'm serious!
聞け！　ホントなんだって
猫の話なら
俺らより水野の方がよくね？
If you wanna talk about cats, go find Mizuno.
She likes cats.
あいつ　猫好きだしな
Mizuno! ...no ...no...
（晴彦）水野～ッ　の～ッ　の～ッ
（楓）なあに？
Yes?
Hey, wai—
ちょッ　お前
やあ　潤平がさあ
Oh, Junpei was—
I-Idiots!
バッ　バカ～ッ！
（担任）おーい　みんな席に着け
ホームルーム　はっじまるよ～
Everyone take your seats.
Homeroom is starting.
Okay.
（生徒達）はーい
戻ってきたねえ
早いねえ
You're back?
That was quick.
うるせッ
Shut up!
Oh, is Sumiyoshi late again?
住吉は　また遅刻か？
しょうがないヤツだな→
She's really hopeless.
It's time to start preparing for the Culture Festival.
ボチボチ文化祭の準備の
時期になりました→
そこで今日はクラスの実行委員を
バトルロワイヤルで…
So today, we'll pick class reps for...
〈あいつら　俺が水野に
気があるのを知ってて〉
They did that on purpose, because they know I have feelings for Mizuno!
〈ぜってー　わざとだろ〉
（千鶴）
うーん　どこかしら　この住所
Where is this address?
I can understand what cats say, huh...
〈猫の言葉がわかる　か…〉
〈はたから見りゃ
親バカな話だよな〉
To others, that's just the crazy talk of a pet owner.
〈しかし…〉
But...
《ヨイショ》
《（物音）》
Crap!
《げッ　ヤベッ》
《大丈夫かな》
Is it all right?
The head!
《首～～ッ！》
昨日のまま…　だよな
Just like yesterday.
Figures.
I don't believe in occult stuff.
〈オカルトのたぐいは信じない〉
〈だが　やっぱりこれって…〉
But is this...
It's a curse.
《呪いニャ～》
Curse
これで何とかなりませんかね？
Can we make a deal about this?
Hell no.
（ニャムサス）なるもんかね
N-Nyamsus!
ニャムサス！
はあ～　なるほどねえ
I see.
高坂家の息子が地蔵様の首をねえ
Kousaka's son broke the head off the cat statue, huh.
ママさんが知ったら泣くわ
Mama-san would cry if she knew about this.
You were watching?!
見てたんすか
Oh, hello there.
（住職）おや　こんにちは
こッ　こんにちは
H-H-Hello.
Taking a walk with your kitty?
猫ちゃんとお散歩中で？
違います　断じてッ
Absolutely not!
I-I see.
そッ　そう…
これは君が供えてくれたのかい？
ありがとうね
Did you put this here?
Thank you.
いえ…
N-No problem.
Are you interested?
君　興味あるの？　この地蔵はね
The statue honors a cat that saved the people of this area from difficulties.
昔この地で　人を災いから
救った猫をまつったものなんだ
けど　正義感が強い分
悪さをすると大変
But because the cat had a very strong sense of righteousness,
その反動で呪われてしまうんだよ
people who treat it badly suffer and are cursed.
いや～　君の行いで
地蔵も喜んでおるだろう
I'm sure the statue is happy with your offering.
動物霊って結構そういうの
見てるっていうしねえ
The animal spirits watch us more than we realize.
その辺　もっと詳しくお願いします
Teach me more about this!
ほう
Yeah?
この地に伝わる猫地蔵が
誕生したのは　かれこれ…
The cat statue in this area was originally found in...
We're starting with the statue's origins?!
〈…って
猫地蔵誕生からスタートかよ〉
〈まさかそれ　全部読む気か？〉
Don't tell me you're gonna read all that.
The time is Kanen, during the middle Edo Period.
時は寛延　江戸時代も半ば過ぎ…
And why did you change your clothes?!
〈しかも何で服　変わってんだ？〉
It has nothing to do with the story!
〈語りと関係ねえだろ〉
てか　何でお前もいんだよ？
Besides, why are you here too?
I know the cat here.
ここんちのやつは知り合いでね
I just came to say hi.
ついでに　あいさつしにきただけさ
げッ　まさか　ここんちも…
You mean there's...
（タマ）あれ　ねえさん
来てたんですかい？
Oh Nee-san, you were around?
タマ　邪魔してるよ
Hi there, Tama.
It's a cat.
やっぱ猫が
そっちの人間は　ねえさんの？
Is that human yours?
ああ　地蔵様の首をポッキリやった
罰当たりさ
Yeah.
He's the sinner who broke off the statue's head.
マジですかい！？
うッ　ニャムめ
Are you serious?!
Damn Nyam!
それでウチのご主人の話を
聞いてるんでやんすね
So, that's why he's listening to my master's story?
ねえさんと違って
愚かなお人ですね
Unlike you, he's an idiot.
〈よくしゃべる猫だな〉
He sure talks a lot.
〈聞こえてんだよ〉
I can hear all that!
Well, all those stories make him sound authoritative,
でも　ウチのご主人
難しいこと言って偉そうですけど
キャバクラ常連の
なまぐさ坊主ですぜ
but actually he's a lazy monk who frequents cabarets.
Oh really?
おや　まあ
キャ　キャバクラ？
C-Cabarets?!
住職の話も聞かずに
何やってんだい
Why are you ignoring the monk's story?
タマ　説明してやっとくれ
Tama, explain it to him.
はい　ねえさん
Okay, Nee-san.
To put it simply...
え～　かいつまんで話しやすと→
怪談の百物語と同じく　ここには
猫の百物語がありやしてね→
Just like in the Hundred Ghost Stories game,
In the "Hundred Ghost Stories" parlor game, a room is illuminated by one hundred candles.
As each guest tells a ghost story, the candles are extinguished one by one.
there are a hundred cat stories.
お猫様に誠意を持って
よい行いをしていけば→
If you revere cats with all your heart,
ろうそくの炎が消えてくように
呪いが解けてくんですが→
your curse will be lifted gradually, like the candle flames going out.
ですがね　猫の声が聞こえる
However...
Being able to understand cats is only the first phase of the curse.
これすなわち　呪いの第一段階
罪滅ぼしせずに　ほっとくと
呪いが進んじまって　しまいには
If you fail to atone,
the curse will get worse, and in the end...
しまいには？
In the end?
猫になりやすぜ
You'll turn into a cat.
フッ　お猫様によい行いだ？
Revere cats with all my heart?
日頃　俺は誰に苦しめられてると
思ってんだ！？
Who the hell do you think causes me grief every day?!
I won't listen, you allergens!
お前ら　アレルゲンの
言いなりになるもんか！
呪いなんか　クソくらえだ！
To hell with the curse!
ほ～ら　言わんこっちゃない
See? We warned you.
〈何だよ　デカい態度とりやがって〉
What? Are you trying to bluff me?
〈あれ？
なんか一段とデカくねえ？〉
Huh?
Aren't you getting bigger?
〈にゃに～ッ！？　猫ににゃってる！〉
What?!
I'm a cat!
〈ヤバイ　自分の毛が器官に…〉
Crap, my fur is in my trachea.
〈苦しい…　たッ　助け…〉
I can't breathe.
H-Help—
〈あッ　死ぬ…〉
I'm dying...
えッ　最終回？
Wha? Final ep?
Mizuno Kaede singing.
水野楓　歌います
Nyan koi, nya nya~
My day off is ruined.
せっかくの休日が　台なしだ
My memory of yesterday is fading in and out.
〈昨日は途中から
記憶があいまいになるし〉
Come listen again!
《また聞きにおいでね》
I'll turn into a cat and die from allergies at this rate.
〈このままだと猫になって
アレルギー死〉
But if I try to work towards a solution, I'll be in allergy hell!
〈けど　呪いを解こうとしても
アレルゲン地獄〉
Oh, Master!
≪（タマ）あッ　ダンナ
About yesterday.
昨日は　どうもです
You again?! And who are you calling "Master"?!
またお前か　誰がダンナだ
What a lazy bum, sleeping past noon.
昼過ぎまで　いいご身分だね
We've got to talk.
話がある　下りてきな
Come down.
〈すげえ　やなんすけど〉
I really don't wanna.
Are you willing to listen?!
話　聞く気あんのかい？
I am!
ある！　が　そっから入ってくんな
But don't cross that line!
Now, talk.
さあ　話せ
聞く態度じゃないですぜ
That's no way to listen, Master.
Anyway, near the apartment complex, a human is molesting stray cats.
実は近頃　近所の団地でノラ達が
人間の被害に遭ってるらしくてね
These kids came to us in tears.
この子らが
泣きついてきたんでさあ
へえ
This person uses sly methods to entice a cat.
≪（タマ）そいつは
巧みな策略で猫を誘い込み→
Once the cat is caught, it's molested without end,
捕らえたが最後
そいつの好きに　もてあそばれ→
and ends up deeply traumatized as a result!
かかわった猫は　みんなノイローゼに
かかっちまってるそうでさあ
Right, guys?
だろ？　お前達
（子猫達）人間　怖～い
Humans are scary!
That's so cruel!
ひでえ話だな　おい
See?
ニャン！
〈しまった　つい…〉
Crap, they tricked me.
Yes! It's cruel!
そうっすよ　ひでえ話っすよ
助けてやっておくんなさい
Help us, Master!
Master!
ダンナ～ッ！
どうでやんすか　ダンナ
How about it, Master?
乗せられてたまるか！
You can't trick me into getting involved!
And you call yourself a man?
あんた　それでも男かい？
Hey Mom, guess what's on sale today?
ねえ　お母さん
今日の特売品って…　うん？
I'm sorry, but don't get me into any more trouble!
わりいけど　やっぱこれ以上
やっかい事に巻き込まないでくれ
（猫達）ニャ～ッ　ニャ～ッ！
潤平兄ちゃん？
Junpei?
Weird.
変なの　どうしちゃったんだろ？
What's got into him?
Excuse me!
すいませーん
あの　昨日お邪魔した者ですが
I was here yesterday!
He's not here?
留守かよ
〈そうさ　別にあいつらの
言いなりにならなくっても〉
Yeah! There's no need to listen to them!
There must be other ways to lift the curse!
呪いを解く方法が
きっと他にあるはずだ！
Sorry.
すいませんした…
Make it quick!
ダッシュでよろしく～
Man, just 'cause Dad's away working, the women of the house treat me like a slave!
親父が単身赴任中だからって
いいように使いやがって
ウチの女どもは
The meat's got to be raw!
やっぱり肉は生よねえ
鮮度が違うわ
It's so fresh!
Mizuno?
水野
高坂君　どうしたの？
Kousaka-kun, why are you carrying those big bags?
その　おっきな荷物
あッ　いや
Well...
悪いな　手　貸してもらっちゃって
Sorry for making you help.
ううん　けど重いね
やっぱ丸々ひと袋　持とうか？
But it sure is heavy.
Should I carry the whole bag?
いや
そこまでしてもらうわけには…
No, I couldn't make you do that much.
You're really great.
偉いな　さすが男の子だね
A true man.
〈父さん　俺　頑張れそうです〉
Dad, I'm going to do my best!
そういえば　それ　何か借りたの？
By the way, did you rent something?
えッ　これ？
Oh, this?
It's...
これは　う～ん…
〈かッ　かわいい
動物モノとか　恋愛モノとかかな〉
S-So cute.
Is it a romance, or about animals?
ちょっと恥ずかしいけど
大好きなんだよね
It's a bit embarrassing, but I really love...
Brides of the Yakuza
このシリーズ
this series!
G-Gangsters?
ごッ　極道モノ！？
Yup!
うん　男気あるもん
大好きなんだよ　私
I love anything with manly spirit.
特に　このパート１０は
超お気に入りでさ～
I especially like this tenth volume.
へえ～
R-Really...
The Boss gets stabbed while protecting his wife.
ドンが　嫁をかばって
刺されるんだけど
He's really manly then!
それが実に男なんだよね
〈笑顔　近え～〉
Her smile is so close to me.
〈ひょっとして俺達
はたから見ると…〉
Do we happen to...
l-l-l-look like we're dating?
〈こッ　恋人同士とかに
見られてたりするのだろうか〉
鼻の下伸ばして
何やってんだかねえ
What is he doing, acting like a slob?
デレデレですね
All lovey-dovey.
お前らッ
Y-You guys!
ダンナ～　そんな犬くせえ女
どこがいいんですかい？
Master, what's so good about a girl who stinks of dogs?
お猫様へのよい行いは
どうした？
What happened to treating cats with reverence?
いまに罰が当たるよ
You'll pay for it.
What?!
何だと？
あッ！
おい　どこ見て歩いてんだい！
Hey! Watch where you're going!
ごめんなさい
I-I'm sorry.
Sorry won't do.
これ　ごめんじゃ済まないよね？
あーッ！
タマ　黙っときな
Tama, keep quiet.
ほれた女を守るのが
男ってもんだ→
It's a man's duty to protect the woman he loves.
それを邪魔しちゃいけないよ
Don't get in his way now.
〈やべえ　これ　どうしよ〉
Crap, what do I do?
本当にごめんなさい
クリーニング代は…
Um, I'm really sorry!
I'll pay for cleaning—
今から大事な人と会うんだよ
時間ないんだよねえ
I was going to see my lover.
I don't have time!
〈水野…〉
Mizuno...
Cut it out already.
もう　そのくらいにしとけよ
謝ってんだろッ
She apologized!
〈とは言ってみたものの〉
That's what I said...
〈死亡フラグ確定～ッ！〉
but it's my death flag, for sure!
すみませんでした
I'm sorry.
あの　クリーニング代…
ホント結構ですんで
Um, the cost of cleaning—
Really, it's okay.
すみませんでした
いえ　こちらこそ→
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
俺のことは忘れてくださーい！
Please forget about this!
Geez!
もう！
ちょいと　タマ
Hey! Tama!
何？　今の
What was that?
ごめんね　高坂君
迷惑かけちゃって
I'm sorry about the trouble, Kousaka-kun.
N-No, don't mention it.
いや　迷惑だなんて
でも　ホントにありがとう
But, thank you so much.
ちょっと　カッコよかったよ
You were pretty cool.
水野…
Mizuno...
You were like the Boss!
ドンみたいだった　カックイイ～！
ドン？
So cool!
The Boss?!
So cool! So cool!
〈しかし　あのオッサンの顔
どっかで見たような…〉
But haven't I seen that man before?
いかん　スーツを着ると
どうも強気に…
Crap, wearing this suit makes me act tough.
当分　この格好は封印せんとなあ
I'd better refrain from dressing like this.
やれやれ　そういうことかい
I see. That's how it is.
Master, you nitwit!
ご主人のバカ～ッ
ねえさん　ねえさん！
Nee-san! Nee-san!
あんた達
助けて　また来たの
You guys.
Help! It's here again!
怖いアイツが～
Scary!
ありがとな　もうこの辺で
Uh, thanks so much. This should be far enough.
Nah, I'll carry it a bit further.
や～　もうちょっとつきあうよ
私もちょうど
こっちに用事あったし
I was headed this way anyway.
What for?
へえ～　用事って？
あッ
どうしたんだよ　急に
What is it, all of a sudden?
Um, Kousaka-kun, I...
その～　高坂君　あのね…
《高坂君　あのね…》
Kousaka-kun, I...
It's a bit embarrassing, but I...
恥ずかしいんだけど　実は私
なッ　ちょッ…
ああ～　もう我慢できない！
Wha?! Wait!
I can't hold back anymore!
嫌いじゃない　全然嫌いじゃない
I don't hate you! I don't hate you at all!
けど　心の準備が～ッ！
But I'm not emotionally ready!
（野良猫）ニャ～ッ！
ほ～ら　ほ～ら　猫ちゃん
Come here, kitty.
おいしいゴハンだよ～
I have yummy food.
Here.
ほれ～　よーし　捕まえた
Gotcha!
もう　恥ずかしがらなくていいのよ
Don't be so bashful!
たっぷり　かわいがっちゃうから
I'll love you to pieces!
D-Don't tell me...
〈まッ　まさか…〉
高坂君も　どう？　かわいいよ
Do you want to pet it too?
He's so cute!
No! No, thank you!
いえ　結構です
そう？　私　猫大好きなんだけど
両親が犬派で
Really?
I love cats, but my parents prefer dogs.
家にもたくさん　わんこいるから
猫　飼えなくて
We have lots of dogs at home, so we can't have cats.
I come here to feed the stray cats and pet them and pet them!
だから　ここのノラちゃんに
ゴハンあげにきては
めいっぱい触らせてもらってるの
Sly methods.
Deeply traumatized.
A-A perfect match for the culprit.
〈犯人像まんまの光景が…〉
てことは　やっぱり…
Does that mean...
Yes, she's our enemy, the one who's been rampaging through this apartment complex.
そう　そいつが最近　この団地を
荒らしてる　私らの天敵さ
Nyamsus!
ニャムサス
やれやれ
I knew she smelled of dogs, but I couldn't believe it was her.
犬くさいとは思ったけど
まさかそのお嬢ちゃんだとはね
ガツンと言ってくだせえ
虐待はやめろ　このアホ女！　って
Go ahead and tell her!
"Stop the abuse, you dumb bitch!"
Go!
言えるかい　このクソ猫ども！
I can't do that, you stupid cats!
あ～ん　おじちゃんが
ノイローゼになっちゃうよ
Uncle will be traumatized!
高坂君　どうしたの？　その猫は？
What's the matter, Kousaka-kun?
Who are those cats?
水野
Mizuno...
〈いかん　せかさんばかりに〉
Crap! The allergy sources are approaching me to force my hand.
〈アレルゲン達が侵入してきている〉
Geez, I have no choice!
〈ええい　こうなったら仕方ない〉
H-Hey...
あのな　気　悪くしないで
聞いてほしいんだけど
I hope you won't be offended by this.
うん？
猫ってさ
It's okay to love cats, but it's not okay to overdo it.
かわいがるのはいいんだけど
構いすぎるのもダメなんだ
See? I think he's had enough.
ほら
そいつも嫌がってるみたいだし
Really?
そうなの？　こんなに
しっぽ振って喜んでるのに？
Even though he's really excited and wagging his tail so much?
It's the opposite for cats, Mizuno.
〈猫は逆だよ　水野〉
〈うらやましくなってきたぞ
猫めッ〉
Damn it, I'm getting envious of that cat!
Hurry the hell up, chicken!
さっさとおし
このヘタレ
〈猫達の鋭い視線が突き刺さる
けど…〉
The cats are staring at me so intently.
But...
私　てっきり
わんこと一緒だと思って
I thought they acted like dogs.
She has no ill intentions.
〈悪気はないんだよな　水野
しかし…〉
But...
ダンナ　ほらガツンと
Master! Tell her!
助けて　助けて～ッ
Help us! Help us!
〈何だ　このワケのわからん
板挟みは〉
Why am I caught like this between a rock and a hard place?!
猫のことで　気　悪くしないで
聞いてほしいんだけど
H-Hey, I hope you won't get offended about the cat...
Second try...
うん？
何が言いたいかと言うと　その…
Well, my point is...
タマ　やるよ
へい！
Tama, let's do it.
Right!
そろそろ放し…
You should let that...
cat...
触んじゃねえ！
Hands off!
あッ　ちッ　違う
N-N-No!
今のは　猫に…
I-I was telling the cats...
ごめんなさい　もうしませーん！
I'm sorry! I won't do it again!
フン　やりゃ　できるじゃないか
それも　また男だよ
You can do it.
Now you're a man.
Although he lost something else.
まッ　違うものを
失ったっぽいすけどね
ダンナ　荷物忘れてますよ
Master! Your bags!
You left your bags!
さあ　これでもう大丈夫だよ
You'll be all right now.
Nee-san!
ねえさん
Nothing good comes from dealing with cats.
〈猫にかかわると
ろくなことがない〉
〈最悪だ〉
This is just crap.
〈昨日はホントに
最悪な一日だった〉
Yesterday was the worst.
〈水野　俺のことなんてもう…〉
I'm sure Mizuno will...
〈避けられたら　どうしよう〉
What if she avoids me?
あッ　高坂君
Oh, Kousaka-kun!
あの…　昨日はごめんね
I'm sorry about yesterday.
私　いつも度が過ぎちゃうみたいで
I guess I tend to go overboard a lot.
あッ　いや　俺の方こそ　ごめん
I'm sorry too.
No, I'll be careful from now on.
ううん　これから気をつけるね
ところで…
By the way...
えッ？
昨日　高坂君のそばにいた
Was the cat with the red scarf yesterday...
赤いスカーフの猫って…
ああ　ウチの飼い猫だけど
Yeah, that's our cat.
うわあ　やっぱり
I knew it!
ねえ　今度会いにいってもいいかな
Hey, can I come see her another day?
猫のこと　もっと教えてほしいし
And you can tell me more about cats.
Yup.
〈いろいろありましたが
どうでもよくなりました〉
A lot has happened, but I no longer care.
〈これからは　また
今までどおりの日常だ〉
My life has returned to normal!
じゃあな
おう
See ya.
Yeah!
普通って　すばらしいな
Normal is wonderful.
おッ　今　お帰りですかい？　ダンナ
You're just heading home, Master?
あれ　おかしいな　まだ聞こえる？
That's weird.
I can still hear them?
（ニャムサス）あんたまさか　あれだけで
呪いが解けたと思ってないかい？
Did you think one deed was sufficient to lift the curse?
違うの？
It wasn't?!
Come on, Master.
やだなあ　ダンナ　僕はちゃんと
百物語って言いやしたぜ
I told you about the Hundred Stories.
てことは　あと９９件！？
You mean I still have ninety-nine to go?!
You'll turn into a cat if you don't.
やんなきゃ猫になっちまうよ
これからも誠意を持って
依頼を片づけるんだね
Revere cats with all your heart from now on.
NOOOOOO!
〈こうして俺の
不幸な日常が始まったのだった〉
That's how my days of misfortune began.
natsu no kaze kirameku machi ni
In this town where the wind sparkles,
nigemizu oikakeru honokana sugata
I see your silhouette chasing a mirage.
shinkokyuu shite oikakeru kedo
You take a deep breath and keep chasing it.
chiisaku kieteyuku senaka ni sotto tsubuyaita
I whisper to your back as you get further away.
nemurenai yoru ni me wo tojite
When I close my eyes on sleepless nights,
omoiegaku mirai niwa
and imagine my future,
futari no egao sore igai ni mou mienai
I can only see the two of us smiling together.
konnani setsunai kimochi
This really sweet, painful thought...
kizuite kurenakutemo
Even if you never notice it,
kokoro ni sotto negau dake
I just wish for it in my mind.
ashita ni nareba kanau hazu
I'm sure it'll come true tomorrow.
surechigatta shunkan ni
At the moment we passed by each other,
waraikakete kureta ne
you gave me a smile.
soredake de mune ga atsui
Just that makes my heart glow,
shiawase dakara
because I'm happy...
because I'm happy.
strawberry kiss
Strawberry kiss.
Today's Nyan Koma!
Today's Mew view
水野んちって犬飼ってんだよな
You have dogs at home, right?
うん　いるよ～
こんな感じ？
Yeah, we do.
Like this?
《よしよし》
Good doggy.
バーニーズとラブと
ハスキーにシェパードかな
Well, we have a Bernese, a Lab, a Husky, and a Shepherd.
えッ　全部　大型犬
しかも軍用犬まで！
They're all large dogs! And military dogs too!
ゾゾッ　犬くせーッ
猫道のオキテ　その１
Mew view
God! So many dogs!
The First Rule of Cats:
私らと仲良くしたきゃ
わんこのにおいは禁物さ
If you want to get along with us, get rid of your dog's stench.
That Guy... A Servant?
Next Time
Anyway, see you next time!